Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪Blossoms rise and scatter never to return♪
♪تزهر الأزهار وتنتشر دون أن تعود♪
♪Time rushes on toward its withering end♪
♪الوقت يتسارع نحو نهايته الذابلة♪
♪Rights and wrongs unfold♪
تتكشف الحقائق والأخطاء
♪Breaking through fate's tightening walls♪
♪اختراق جدران القدر المشددة♪
♪Few ever find their way home♪
♪قلما يجد أحد طريقه إلى المنزل♪
♪Through storms and drifting snow as silver hair falls♪
♪عبر العواصف والثلوج المتراكمة بينما يتساقط الشعر الفضي♪
♪A lifetime of ruin for one bitter revel♪
♪حياة من الخراب من أجل احتفال مرير واحد♪
♪A single dream born from a single thought♪
♪حلم واحد ولد من فكرة واحدة♪
♪Shattered at a touch♪
♪تحطم عند لمسة♪
♪When the dream fades I look once more♪
♪عندما يتلاشى الحلم أنظر مرة أخرى♪
=Aligned Reverence=
=الاحترام المتوافق=
(Adapted from Jinyi's novel of the same name on Qimao Novel)
(مقتبس من رواية جيني التي تحمل نفس الاسم على Qimao Novel)
=Episode 14= (It was my selfish hope)
=الحلقة 14= (كان ذلك أملي الأناني)
Yunxi.
يونكسي.
Yan.
نعم.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Did something happen at home?
هل حدث شيء في المنزل؟
No.
لا.
I... I just feel that
أنا... أشعر بذلك فقط
I owe you.
أنا مدين لك.
No, I owe you.
لا، أنا مدين لك.
The weight of the Xiao family
ثقل عائلة شياو
has fallen on you alone.
لقد وقع الأمر عليك وحدك.
Right,
يمين،
how is the grain procurement going?
كيف تسير عملية شراء الحبوب؟
Very smoothly.
بسلاسة تامة.
Almost too smoothly.
بسلاسة مفرطة تقريباً.
It makes me uneasy.
إنه يجعلني أشعر بعدم الارتياح.
Everyone in the family,
جميع أفراد العائلة،
especially...
خصوصاً...
They...
هم...
They are gambling everything
إنهم يقامرون بكل شيء
just for my future.
فقط من أجل مستقبلي.
I...
أنا...
I know.
أنا أعرف.
It's hard.
إنه صعب.
But you must
ولكن يجب عليك
hold on and keep going.
تمسك بالأمل واستمر في التقدم.
Only then will you not fail the one who cares most for you.
عندها فقط لن تخذل من يهتم بك أكثر من غيره.
All right.
حسنًا.
Since it's going well,
بما أن الأمور تسير على ما يرام،
I'll contact our old retainers.
سأتصل بمحامينا السابقين.
They'll support you when needed.
سيدعمونك عند الحاجة.
Go back now.
ارجع الآن.
Okay.
تمام.
(Yunyan, I know.)
(يون يان، أعرف ذلك.)
(You won't let that person down.)
(لن تخذل ذلك الشخص.)
Young Madam. Your five shops and the property in the west of the city
سيدتي الشابة. لديكِ خمسة متاجر وعقار في غرب المدينة
(Storage Room) have all been converted to banknotes
تم تحويل جميع (غرفة التخزين) إلى أوراق نقدية
and handed to Heir Qi for grain.
وتم تسليمها إلى هير تشي مقابل الحبوب.
However,
لكن،
the broker said when the shops were sold, the Su mother and daughter came to inquire.
قال الوسيط إنه عندما تم بيع المحلات، جاءت الأم وابنتها سو للاستفسار.
They're stockpiling grain as well.
إنهم يقومون بتخزين الحبوب أيضاً.
My aunt has always been cunning.
لطالما كانت عمتي ماكرة.
Let them stockpile if they want.
دعهم يخزنوا ما يريدون.
Everyone, work hard tonight.
يا جماعة، اجتهدوا الليلة.
Take turns keeping watch.
تناوبوا على الحراسة.
All right.
حسنًا.
Make sure the grain doesn't get wet.
تأكد من عدم تبلل الحبوب.
Slow down.
ابطئ.
Why push yourself so hard?
لماذا تضغط على نفسك بهذا الشكل؟
Here in the Xiao family,
هنا في عائلة شياو،
everyone treats me so well.
الجميع يعاملني معاملة حسنة للغاية.
I want to do more for them.
أريد أن أفعل المزيد من أجلهم.
And everything you do,
وكل ما تفعله،
isn't it also for me?
أليس هذا الأمر يخصني أيضاً؟
Little Yuan.
يوان الصغير.
Could it be
هل يمكن أن يكون
the coffin shop isn't doing well,
متجر التوابيت لا يسير على ما يرام.
and you're planning to support their business?
وهل تخطط لدعم أعمالهم؟
Physician Xi.
الطبيب شي.
Mind your tongue.
احذر من لسانك.
Or else
وإلا
you might get thrown out.
قد يتم طردك.
Throw me out?
طردني ؟
Fine.
بخير.
I'll leave then.
سأغادر إذن.
I won't disturb you, Young Master Xie,
لن أزعجك يا سيد شيه الشاب.
while you fawn over Little Yuan.
بينما تتودد إلى ليتل يوان.
(Feiwan Pavilion)
(جناح فيوان)
Thanks for coming all this way with me.
شكراً لقدومك معي طوال هذه المسافة.
You're not going in?
أنت لا تذهب؟
Standing here like a stone waiting for your wife?
هل تقف هنا كالحجر تنتظر زوجتك؟
I'll just take one look.
سألقي نظرة واحدة فقط.
Young Lady Xi, thank you for your trouble.
السيدة الشابة شي، شكراً لكِ على جهدكِ.
Please bring the medicine inside.
يرجى إحضار الدواء إلى الداخل.
This...
هذا...
Third Sister-in-law specially made this porridge for you.
قامت أخت الزوج الثالثة بإعداد هذه العصيدة خصيصاً لك.
Drink it.
اشربه.
And take your medicine.
وتناول دوائك.
I understand.
أفهم.
Just leave it here.
اتركه هنا.
I'll check the account book.
سأراجع دفتر الحسابات.
Drink the porridge while it's still warm.
اشرب العصيدة وهي لا تزال دافئة.
Okay.
تمام.
I'll go close the door.
سأذهب وأغلق الباب.
Yunxi.
يونكسي.
Since you're back,
بما أنك عدت،
why not go inside?
لماذا لا تدخل إلى الداخل؟
No need.
لا حاجة.
I still can't show myself before her.
ما زلت لا أستطيع أن أظهر نفسي أمامها.
Besides,
بجانب،
you're taking good care of her.
أنت تعتني بها جيداً.
It's because...
إنه بسبب...
Because she caught a chill.
لأنها أصيبت بنزلة برد.
I panicked at the time and...
شعرت بالذعر حينها و...
I know.
أنا أعرف.
She's ill.
إنها مريضة.
You're just caring for her.
أنت فقط تعتني بها.
Drink the medicine.
اشرب الدواء.
If you ask me,
إذا سألتني،
your illness isn't only from the cold.
مرضك ليس ناتجاً عن البرد فقط.
It comes from your heart as well.
إنه ينبع من قلبك أيضاً.
What heart ailment could I have?
ما هو مرض القلب الذي قد أعاني منه؟
Is Young Master Xie
هل السيد الشاب شيه
not the cause?
أليس هذا هو السبب؟
Do you take me for a fool?
أتظنني أحمق؟
Ning.
و.
Don't speak recklessly.
لا تتحدث بتهور.
He's only my sixth younger brother.
إنه أخي السادس الأصغر مني فقط.
I cannot fail the Xiao family again.
لا يمكنني أن أخذل عائلة شياو مرة أخرى.
Then will you fail yourself instead?
هل ستخذل نفسك بدلاً من ذلك؟
Yunxi.
يونكسي.
It's all my fault.
كل هذا خطأي.
I was the one who let foolish feelings grow. I...
أنا من سمحت للمشاعر السخيفة بالنمو. أنا...
Yan.
نعم.
Actually, I...
في الحقيقة، أنا...
In any case,
على أي حال،
Xiao Yunxi is already dead.
لقد ماتت شياو يونشي بالفعل.
The one living now
الشخص الذي يعيش الآن
is merely
هو مجرد
ashes rekindled by Physician Xi's furnace.
رمادٌ أُعيد إشعاله بواسطة فرن الطبيب شي.
Yuan is a good girl.
يوان فتاة طيبة.
Take good care of her.
اعتني بها جيدا.
If...
لو...
If it were possible,
لو كان ذلك ممكناً،
I wish you could...
أتمنى لو تستطيع...
When we were young,
عندما كنا صغارا،
whenever I wanted something,
كلما أردت شيئًا،
you always gave it to me.
كنت دائماً تعطيني إياه.
It's my fault.
هذا خطأي.
From today on,
من اليوم فصاعدا،
I will never cross the line again.
لن أتجاوز الخط مرة أخرى.
If...
لو...
Yan.
نعم.
If there's even the slightest chance,
إن كان هناك أدنى احتمال،
I will never let her go so easily.
لن أتركها ترحل بهذه السهولة أبداً.
Only...
فقط...
If one day Xiao Yunxi truly returns,
إذا عادت شياو يونشي يوماً ما،
will you really feel at ease
هل ستشعر حقًا بالراحة؟
being Yan's Sister-in-law?
كونها أخت زوجة يان؟
This bracelet
هذا السوار
was meant for Yunxi's wife.
كان مخصصًا لزوجة يونكسي.
Yunxi would be happy to see it.
سيكون يونشي سعيداً برؤيته.
Life is short.
الحياة قصيرة.
Youth slips away quickly.
الشباب يزول سريعاً.
Never wrong yourself.
لا تخطئ على نفسك أبدًا.
And never wrong others.
ولا تظلم الآخرين أبداً.
Yuan.
يوان.
Careful.
كن حذرا.
Go check on her.
اذهب واطمئن عليها.
All right.
حسنًا.
(Feiwan Pavilion)
(جناح فيوان)
Still just a child.
ما زال طفلاً.
You can't hide anything.
لا يمكنك إخفاء أي شيء.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
I just wasn't careful.
لم أكن حذراً فحسب.
Be careful when going in and out.
كن حذراً عند الدخول والخروج.
Don't you know patients can't catch cold?
ألا تعلم أن المرضى لا يصابون بنزلات البرد؟
Little Yuan.
يوان الصغير.
I've said everything I needed to say.
لقد قلت كل ما كنت بحاجة إلى قوله.
The rest...
البقية...
You should think about carefully.
عليك التفكير في الأمر ملياً.
What did
ماذا فعلت
she say?
قالت؟
No...
لا...
Nothing.
لا شئ.
Yan.
نعم.
The garrison is busy with military duties.
الحامية منشغلة بالمهام العسكرية.
I have Physician Xi here
لدي الطبيب شي هنا
and Third Sister-in-law.
وزوجة الأخ الثالثة.
You don't need to come over for now.
لستَ بحاجة للمجيء الآن.
♪Blossoms rise and scatter never to return♪
♪تزهر الأزهار وتنتشر دون أن تعود♪
When the weather clears,
عندما يتحسن الطقس،
I want to take Yunxi's things
أريد أن آخذ أغراض يونشي
out to dry under the sun.
اتركها لتجف تحت أشعة الشمس.
♪Rights and wrongs unfold♪
تتكشف الحقائق والأخطاء
♪Ever changing, helpless as we are♪
♪متغيرون باستمرار، عاجزون كما نحن♪
♪No right, no wrong♪
♪لا صواب، لا خطأ♪
♪Spring fades, autumn returns, all has changed with time♪
♪يتلاشى الربيع، ويعود الخريف، كل شيء تغير مع مرور الوقت♪
♪Memories drift like smoke, we meet then fall apart♪
♪تتلاشى الذكريات كالدخان، نلتقي ثم نفترق♪
Well.
حسنًا.
♪Over and over again♪
♪مرة تلو الأخرى♪
Take care and focus on recovering.
اعتني بنفسك وركز على التعافي.
♪Few ever find their way home♪
♪قلما يجد أحد طريقه إلى المنزل♪
♪Through storms and drifting snow as silver hair falls♪
♪عبر العواصف والثلوج المتراكمة بينما يتساقط الشعر الفضي♪
♪A lifetime of ruin for one bitter revel♪
♪حياة من الخراب من أجل احتفال مرير واحد♪
♪A single vow was spoken♪
♪ تم النطق بقسم واحد ♪
♪Yet a lifetime of regret remains♪
♪ومع ذلك لا تزال هناك حياة من الندم♪
♪How should one face such pain?♪
♪كيف ينبغي للمرء أن يواجه مثل هذا الألم؟♪
♪Through storms and snow, still without regret♪
♪عبر العواصف والثلوج، ولا زلتُ بلا ندم♪
♪A tangle of love and hate leaves only sorrow behind♪
♪تشابك الحب والكراهية لا يترك وراءه سوى الحزن♪
♪A single dream born from a single thought♪
♪حلم واحد ولد من فكرة واحدة♪
♪Shattered at a touch♪
♪تحطم عند لمسة♪
♪When the dream fades I look once more♪
♪عندما يتلاشى الحلم أنظر مرة أخرى♪
♪Through storms and drifting snow as silver hair falls♪
♪عبر العواصف والثلوج المتراكمة بينما يتساقط الشعر الفضي♪
♪A lifetime of ruin for one bitter revel♪
♪حياة من الخراب من أجل احتفال مرير واحد♪
♪A single vow was spoken♪
♪ تم النطق بقسم واحد ♪
♪Yet a lifetime of regret remains♪
♪ومع ذلك لا تزال هناك حياة من الندم♪
♪How should one face such pain?♪
♪كيف ينبغي للمرء أن يواجه مثل هذا الألم؟♪
♪Through storms and snow, still without regret♪
♪عبر العواصف والثلوج، ولا زلتُ بلا ندم♪
♪A tangle of love and hate leaves only sorrow behind♪
♪تشابك الحب والكراهية لا يترك وراءه سوى الحزن♪
♪A single dream born from a single thought♪
♪حلم واحد ولد من فكرة واحدة♪
♪Shattered at a touch♪
♪تحطم عند لمسة♪
♪When the dream fades I look once more♪
♪عندما يتلاشى الحلم أنظر مرة أخرى♪
♪Blossoms rise and scatter never to return♪
♪تزهر الأزهار وتنتشر دون أن تعود♪
♪Time rushes on toward its withering end♪
♪الوقت يتسارع نحو نهايته الذابلة♪
♪Rights and wrongs unfold♪
تتكشف الحقائق والأخطاء
♪Ever changing, helpless as we are♪
♪متغيرون باستمرار، عاجزون كما نحن♪
♪No right, no wrong♪
♪لا صواب، لا خطأ♪